What Christmas treat am I? What Christmas treat are you?
That is what we are going to find out, so I will leave you the link so that you can take the quiz yourself.
Let us begin.
We can finally do a test that tells you which typical Christmas treat you are.
We were looking forward to it.
Choose an ornament: let's see. They're all ugly, wow, ugly, ugly.
This is the ugliest and this is the simplest.
I don't like the glitter ones very much ...
I'm going to take the little tree, because the ones with glitter,
the glitter stays everywhere and it's a nuisance.
A nuisance.
Choose a tinsel: There are black, blue, gold, white, red and green.
Uh! Via El Corte Inglés. I knew it!
This tinsel seems to be from El CorteInglés.
In case you don't know what El CorteInglés is,
it is a shopping center and its color is green.
El CorteIngles's brand color is  this tinsel's green.
Thus discarded.
I think golden. Gold and red go very well together.
I'm thinking a lottoo mucch about this, gold and that's it.
Choose a date: Christmas Eve, Christmas, New Year's Eve, Kings.
Ok this is complicated. Christmas Eve is December 24th.
Christmas is December 25th.
New Year's Eve is December 31st, the last day of the year: the day of the grapes.
And kings is January 5, because in Spain we have Santa Claus and Three Wise Men.
Santa Claus is coming on the 24th and the Magi are coming on January 5, 5.
Customize the Navity Scene with one of these extras.
I explained to you what the Nativity Scene was,
and see, these are extra decorations for the Nativity Scene.
I'm going to put this one that looks like a water fountain,
because there are some Nativity Scenes that have real water and are cool.
The rest are very simple this is a well, a mill and a bridge.
Open a gift: this one. Because it is yellow.
But I want to see what's inside! Anyway.
Argue about something with your family: politics.
Your studies or your work.
Your love life ... I don't have one.
Family quarrels: every day. This one was easy.
Sing a Christmas carol: ok
El tamborilero doesn't come to me right now.
Well, I choose December 25. Because yes, I like it.
Choose a tree: this is very ugly, this one too, this one too.
Why do they cut it in half and put it in two colors? What kind of aesthetics is that?
Zero.
Ugly, ugly and ugly. This one isn't bad and this one isn't bad.
This one because it looks like a more realistic pine ... Right?
No ... I like this one better.
Accidentally break a ball: the ugliest ... Ok, this is the ugliest.
Who puts stars on a ball? I mean how tacky.
Choose a snoflake, a little snowflake. Let's see ... this one. If I think about it a lot, I'll stay here until tomorrow.
Put a sock even if you don't have a chimney: this one.
You are: if you were a Christmas treat you would be the ferrero, ferrero rocher.
You have a vocation and it is to contradict everything.
You hit the nail on the head kid.
You consider that sleeping with any garment is a barbarian custom.
That's not true, I sleep with whatever.
You prefer musicals to movies where nobody sings.
I hate, I hate musicals and I hate movies with people singing.
Well I'm not going to say that I hate musicals ...
But I don't like it when the plot stops and they start singing.
I want to know what happens, I am not interested in your singing. Ok?
Pipes tijuana to death: yes true, true, true, true, true.
In Spain we eat a lot of pipas and these are pipas Tijuana.
Try them, they are very good.
You suck them and then and you eat them, what is inside.
In Spain we eat a lot of pipas, abroad I haven't seen people eat many pipas ...
It's a bit weird, because they are very good.
I'm a 50% a ferrero rocher, because two of the statements have hit the mark,
and the other two couldn't be more wrong.
Not bad, not bad.
If you do the test, tell me what you get, tell me what treat you are, leave a comment,
and click on subscribe and like and do whatever you want because it's almost Christmas.
Bye.